So I want to ask pi something, let me reload it at first.
So there's something I want to ask pi, and it's about the difference, the actual difference
that it has with the other chatbots.
So I want to say, hey, pi, we're discovering AI chatbots, all the AI chatbots out there.
And I want to ask you a simple question.
I actually want it to ask you about the difference you make.
So I want it to know what is different in you with the other tools out there.
And what are the use cases that you can help us most with, help us the most with, right?
So I ask my question, and I wait for, that's a great question.
What sets me apart from other chatbots is my focus on providing a personalized experience.
I'm not just here to answer questions.
Yes, as you see, personalized experience, so these are about it being emotion, no, right?
So I'm here to build a relationship with you and tell them my responses to individual needs,
right?
Either restaurant recommendation either help planning a trip, right?